[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a philologist study?", "correct_answer": "language", "incorrect_answers": ["signs and  symbols", "art", "detectives"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Mr. Freeze in the 1997 movie Batman and Robin?", "correct_answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "incorrect_answers": ["Pat Hingle", "Victor Fries", "Tommy Lee Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1962 John Steinbeck published Travels with Charley: In Search of America. Who was Charley?", "correct_answer": "Steinbecks pet poodle", "incorrect_answers": ["Steinbecks son from his marriage to Edith Wharton", "Steinbecks wife, Charlotta Pierce", "Steinbecks best friend, Charles Kuralt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the original The Longest Yard first hit the movie theatres in the U.S.?", "correct_answer": "1974", "incorrect_answers": ["1980", "1977", "1971"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Norbit, Rasputias dance teacher regards himself as which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Power Tap Guru", "incorrect_answers": ["Pope of Pop", "Tap Dancing Master", "Jesus of Dance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Glycolipids in cell membranes are involved in transport, enzymatic activity, intercellular joining, and cell-cell recognition.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A death erection is a post-mortem erection which occurs when a male individual dies vertically or face-down.  What causes this condition?", "correct_answer": "Gravity causes the genitalia to fill up with blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Having intercourse before death", "The body swells up", "Bladder and Intestines empty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Topper movies, what was the last name of the married ghosts who haunted Topper?", "correct_answer": "Kerby", "incorrect_answers": ["King", "Krammer", "Kingston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does acrophobia mean?", "correct_answer": "heights", "incorrect_answers": ["snake", "farm", "pain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous mountain flower, endangered in many countries, is the national flower of Switzerland and Austria.", "correct_answer": "Edelweiss", "incorrect_answers": ["Petunia", "Lilly", "Heliconia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the bread called Pane carasau originate?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "Portugal", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of George and Louise Jeffersons son on All in the Family?", "correct_answer": "Lionel", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamar", "Keon", "Tyrone"]}]